———— 德古拉 ————
第一季第一集
——— 真爱字幕组 ———
出  品
翻译：幸福ing形式  火星人善良凡凡
翻译：资本论and圣经  yiyi1461474099
实习翻译：江米球  波波不是花椰菜怪物
校对：laomashitu1  幸福ing形式
组长：火星人善良凡凡
监制：幸福ing形式
1881年  罗马尼亚
本字幕纯属学习交流
===原创翻译  转载标明===
招贤纳士：QQ群233183580
===如有翻译疏忽  还请指正原谅===
————祝大家观影愉快————
历久数载…
After all these long years...
你将变得多么饥饿
how famished you must be.
哦  Jezebel啊
Oh, sweet Jezebel.
快瞧！
Look!
我们发了！
We're rich!
血  就是生命
The blood is the life.
宾客均至
All the guests have arrived.
（1896年  伦敦）
入境时需拍照？
Photographed upon entry?
（1896年  伦敦）
例行安排而已
As arranged.
蓝本如此？
And the prototype?
准备好按规划演示了吗？
Ready for the demonstration as scheduled?
是的  先生
It is, sir.
依安排行事
As scheduled.
从今天开始
From this day forward,
你是一个美国实业家
you are an American industrialist.
以美国之神  枪
As American as God, guns,
以及波旁威士忌的身份…
and bourbon...
- 那就依预计行事  - 很好  先生
- As scheduled. - Very good, sir.
晚上好啊
Good evening.
我是Alexander Grayson
I'm Alexander Grayson.
真是激动人心
It's breathtaking.
哇噢  难道不令人兴奋吗？
Well, isn't this exciting?
- 我开始喜欢上这个Grayson了  - 谢谢
- I'm liking this Grayson already. - Thank you.
这杯子的价值比我一周赚得都多
This glass is worth more than I earn in a week.
别显得那么土气  Jonathan
Don't be gauche, Jonathan
再说…它比你一个月赚的还多
Besides...it's worth more than you make in a month.
Lucy！
Lucy!
我就开了个玩笑
I'm only having a bit of fun.
你该不会生我气吧？
You're not cross with me, are you?
我会受打击的
I'd be simply devastated.
当然没有  你是那么迷人
Of course not. You're far too charming.
确实啊  不是吗？
I am, aren't I?
我得走了
I'm off.
那  你会记得你的承诺  对吗？
Now, you'll remember your promise, won't you?
今夜我是你的客人  不是新闻工作者
I'm your guest tonight, not a journalist.
他真可爱  对吗？
He's such a darling, isn't he?
Alastair！  你这个坏蛋
Alastair! You beast.
你躲哪儿了？
Where have you been hiding?
Lucy  亲爱的
Lucy, darling.
真是兼容并收的圈子
It's quite an eclectic group.
新高富帅  旧老太爷  还有无产左派
New money, old money, no money left.
你猜猜Alexander Grayson是哪个？
Which do you suppose is Alexander Grayson?
我想他肯定会大张旗鼓地介绍自己
I'm sure he'll announce himself to great fanfare.
- 他们都是这样做事儿的  - 恩
- They always do at these things. - Hmm.
我怎么会让你和我谈论这些…
How I ever let you talk me into this...
说真的  有人想窥探你出实验室
Seriously, somebody had to pry you out of that laboratory.
事实是
The truth.
你愿意和我共度今晚呢
Who would you rather spend your evening with me,
还是说和醉酒蛤蟆呢？
or a pickled toad?
哈  蛤蟆吧…
Um, the toad...
因为  最后还有机会
Because at least there's a chance
吻的他青蛙变王子
my kiss might turn him into a prince.
哇噢  他很努力吗？
Well, hasn't he tried hard?
也许是用英镑当墙纸贴
Might as well have papered the walls with pound notes.
多么令人不安的美国啊
How distressingly American.
坦白说  我很惊讶这么多人会出席
Frankly, I'm amazed so many of us turned up at all.
如果我们目不直视
How can we properly mock him
我们该怎样恰当的嘲笑他们呢？
if we haven't set eyes on the man?
女士们先生们  很荣幸向你介绍
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my pleasure to introduce
卡菲克斯庄园主  宴会东道主
the master of Carfax Manor, your host,
Alexander Grayson先生
Mister Alexander Grayson!
- 是他啊  - 是他！
- It's him. - It's him!
欢迎宾至
Welcome to my house.
期望你们来的自由  去的安逸
May you come freely, go safely,
也请你们留下一点快乐和幸福
and please, leave some of the happiness you bring.
没事吧？
Is everything all right?
- 没事  - 你确定？
- Yes. - Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
我就  我刚打了个寒颤
Someone walked over my grave, I suppose.
恩哼
Hmm.
那个女人  蓝绸裙  乳纱缎
That woman. Blue satin, creme chiffon.
我想知晓她的一切
I want to know everything about her,
- 还有和她一起的那个男的  - 好的  先生
- and the man she's with. - Of course, sir.
啊  神秘的Grayson先生
Ah, the mysterious Mister Grayson.
我们还是见面了
Finally we meet.
你是？
And you would be?
好吧  我本应置身于温暖浴室
Well, I would be in a nice warm bath,
但却不得不来
but I simply had to come
看看这儿发生了什么破事
and find out what all the fuss was about.
- Jayne Wetherby  - 恩
- Jayne Wetherby. - Hmm.
这是Wetherby大人？
Lord Wetherby?
哦  拜托  不是！
Oh, good God, no!
这是我的  恩  今夜的男伴儿
This is my, um, companion for the night,
我的好朋友  Herr Kruger
my very dear friend, Herr Kruger.
为康健干杯
Gesundheit.
啊  我是Clive Dawes
Ah. Sir Clive Dawes.
Alexander Grayson
Alexander Grayson.
请允许我介绍我的夫人  Hope
Permit me to introduce my wife, Lady Hope.
这真是一个难以让人忘怀的舞厅
What an impressive ballroom,
Grayson先生
Mister Grayson.
还有Davenport大人…
May I present Lord Davenport...
Laurent女士…
And Lady Laurent...
以及Laurent大人
And Lord Laurent.
Laurent大人
Lord Laurent.
好极了  那  如果我没记错
Splendid. Now, if I'm not mistaken,
你和Clive先生共同主事
you and sir Clive co-chair
大英因皮里尔冷剂公司的董事会
the board of British Imperial Coolant Company.
我们只是董事一员  Grayson先生
We sit on a number of boards, Mister Grayson.
事实上你就是
Indeed you do.
大英因皮里尔拥有专利
British Imperial holds patents,
高效冷冻剂的专利
patents to high-efficiency coolants
这对加快我的一个技术项目
which would be most useful in advancing one of
是非常有用的
my technological projects.
我想拿到这些专利
I would very much like to acquire those patents.
Grayson先生  大英冷剂公司的任务
Mister Grayson, the British Imperial Company
是把自己的产品
is in the business of selling our products
卖给英国企业
to British industry,
而不是把我们潜在的专利
not our underlying patents
送来共同殖民地
to interloping colonials.
亲爱的
Darling.
也许下次
Perhaps next time
你会让Clive先生
you'll sway sir Clive
改变主意
through his bookmakers.
据我所知
He's an inveterate gambler,
他有赌博的陋习
not a terribly good one
而且这可不是个好习惯
from what I gather.
Jonthan！ 你跑去哪里了…
Jonathan! Where did you run...
- Alexander Grayson   - Jonathan Harker.
- Alexander Grayson. - Jonathan Harker.
这个是我最可爱的朋友
And this is my most lovely friend,
Mina Murray小姐
Miss Mina Murray.
当然  Mina
Of course. Mina.
我很抱歉  只是…
I'm sorry, it's just...
- 我发誓…  - 我们曾经见过？
- I'd swear... - We've met?
是的
Yes.
我也有同感
I was thinking the same thing.
打扰 先生
Pardon me, sir.
- 时间到了  - 啊 对
- It's time. - Ah, yes.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
告诉我 Renfeild，
Tell me, Renfield.
Jonathan Harker 是谁？
Who is this Jonathan Harker?
审判者报的记者
He's a reporter for the Inquisitor.
手上握有很多资源 很精明
Resourceful, tenacious,
而且非常非常有野心
and very, very ambitious.
恩  那个女的呢？
Hmm. And the woman?
Mina Murray  医学生
Mina Murray, medical student.
老爸是William Murray医生
Father, Doctor William Murray,
Bethelem Royal医院的院长
director of Bethlem Royal Hospital.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请集中到舞厅中间来
please, gather in the center of the ballroom.
Harker先生  Arem Renfield
Mister Harker. Arem Renfield.
你知道请柬上写明了
You're aware that the invitation
拒绝采访吗？
explicitly forbade the press?
我可以跟你保证
I can assure you,
我只是来社交的
I'm purely here on a social basis.
真遗憾
What a shame.
Grayson先生会很失望的
Mister Grayson will be disappointed
没想到你一个字都不会写
that you won't be writing at least a word or two.
如果你感兴趣  他愿意邀请
If you're interested, he would like you
你明天来专访
to come by tomorrow for an interview.
一个…一个专访？
An... An interview?
当然  我很感兴趣
Of course, I'd be interested.
那么  4点半
430, then.
现在  Grayson先生愿意跟大家分享
And now, Mister Grayson would like to share
他最近的技术成果的展示！
a demonstration of his latest technical marvel!
亲爱的来宾…
Honored guests...
当我还是个小男孩的时候
When I was a boy,
我老爸给我讲了黑暗时代的故事
my father told me stories of the dark ages,
那时候只有野蛮的战争和部族
a time when culture
文化和学习在那个年代
and learning were eclipsed
黯然失色
by barbaric ritual and war.
经过这些年
Over the years,
我已经渐渐相信
I have come to believe that
那个黑暗的时代并没有完全结束
the dark ages never actually ended,
而且恐惧…
that the fear...
仇恨 还有凶残
hatred, and brutality
这些曾经折磨过我们祖先的东西
that once plagued our ancestors
还在折磨着我们
plagues us still.
今晚
Tonight,
是我无上的荣耀
it is my sublime pleasure
来给你们展示一条光明大道
to demonstrate a way out.
一条能走出这个黑暗的时代的光明大道
Out of the darkness.
汤姆生 爱迪生曾经认为它不过是个空想
What Thomas Edison dismissed as mere fantasy,
而尼古拉 特斯拉也没能成就它
what Nikola Tesla failed to bring to fruition,
但是我今晚却能展示给你们
I give to you tonight.
从磁层圈获取的能量
Power drawn from the magnetosphere,
这个无影无形的能量来源
the same invisible source
正是指南针能指方向的原因
that compels the needle on this compass to point North.
经过我的科学家们
Harnessed and amplified by my scientists
和技术员们处理和放大
and technicians,
我能给予你们免费的…
I give to you free...
安全的
safe,
不需要线网的能源
wireless power.
现在  第一步
Now. Stage one.
大家听令！
Stand by!
第一阶段！
Stage one!
开始！
Mark!
这事可能吗？
Is such a thing possible?
从理论上来说可以 我猜
In theory, I suppose.
但是若真的进入市场
But if it were brought to the market,
会对石油能源是多大的冲击啊？
what effect would it have on our petroleum interests?
粉碎性的 当然
Shattering, of course.
没什么好担心的
Nothing we need worry about.
加大功率
More power.
第二阶段！
Stage two!
Lucy
Lucy.
Lucy  快看
Lucy, look.
只是个把戏罢了
Some sort of trick.
肯定有根导线的
There must be a wire.
—— 德古拉 ——
- 啊 快把它关了 现在！ - 啊啊！
- Ah, shut that down, now! - Aah!
我们正经历一些技术难题  先生
Experiencing some technical difficulties, sir.
只需再多几秒而已
Just a few more seconds.
谁来救救我们！
Somebody help us!
我要着了！ 我要着了！
I'm burning! I'm burning!
冷却剂已经挥发了！
The coolant has evaporated!
我正在关！
I'm shutting down!
- 肯定只是个把戏  - 只是个把戏
- It's a trick. - It's a trick.
先生们 女士们
Ladies and gentlemen,
谢谢你们的耐心
I thank you for your patience.
我相信我们的小演示
I trust our little demonstration was...
很有启发意义
illuminating.
Lucy Westenra
Lucy Westenra.
Westenra 小姐
Miss Westenra.
真令人陶醉
Ravishing.
Murray小姐  你看起来有点被吓到了
Miss Murray, you look a little shaken.
我不确定我刚目睹了什么
I'm not sure what I've just witnessed.
未来  Murray小姐
The future, Miss Murray.
一个新时代的开始
The beginning of a new era.
Harker先生
Mister Harker.
- 那么 明天  - 好的
- Tomorrow, then. - Yes.
恩 当然
Yes, of course.
那小子好像深深地迷上你了
He seems quite taken with you.
哎呦喂
Ooh.
那个名叫嫉妒的怪兽
The green-eyed monster
在你心头作祟了哦
rears his ugly head.
Grayson先生不过是出于礼貌
Mister Grayson is just being polite.
我敢说 那并不只是社交礼节
More than polite, I'd say.
好吧！我喝餐后酒去
Ooh! Cordials.
刚才的事真是不同寻常啊
That was extraordinary.
Jayne小姐
Lady Jayne.
我都没感觉到你的到来
I didn't hear you approaching.
Grayson先生 听您的语气
You say that as
仿佛这是我的一种了不起的能力
if it's an accomplishment, Mr. Grayson.
叫我Alexander吧
Alexander, please.
Alexander  你知道吗
You know, there's a touch of
连经理都被你深深触动了
the impresario about you, Alexander.
你今晚的展示
Your performance this evening
简直如歌剧般激动人心
was no less than operatic.
介于我是歌剧的狂热票友
As I'm an ardent patron of the opera,
我就把这当做是对自己的恭维了
I'll take that as a compliment,
虽然我很清楚  真实的情况
although I'm certain it was meant
与你的赞美截然不同
as quite the opposite.
哦 怎么会呢？
Oh, you are?
所以说你居然喜欢歌剧？
So you love the opera?
太好了 我能成为第一个
Well, may I be the first
邀请你参加本轮歌剧献映季开幕的人吗？
to invite you to the opening of the season?
Alexander 你就明说
Tell me, Alexander,
愿不愿意和我同去啊？
will you join me?
- 我已经订好自己的包厢了  - 好遗憾啊
- I've reserved my own box. - Pity.
我想要是你在我的包厢
I feel you'd enjoy the performance
一定会更加享受精彩的表演
so much more in mine.
一定会是那样的
No doubt.
诶
Hmm.
承蒙您的大驾光临不胜感激
Thank you for coming.
我可以吻您的手吗？
May I?
-Grayson先生- 您好
- Mister Grayson. - Ah.
要是你觉得就凭你今晚荒唐的把戏
If you think you fooled anyone
就能骗过哪个傻子的的话
with that absurd stunt tonight,
那你可是大错特错了
you are sadly mistaken.
我真的如此不堪？
Am I?
你就是个骗子 小子
You are a fraud, sir.
而且我保证
And I will see to it
你绝不会再有机会在这里耍花招
that you never do business here.
她是不会在原地一直等你的
She's not going to wait forever.
你若不及时求婚
If you don't ask her to marry you soon,
别人就会取而代之
someone else is bound to.
-哪个混球？-Grayson？
- Who? - Grayson?
你可别傻了
Don't be absurd.
你一定没有注意到
You must've noticed
他是怎样深情的凝望着你
the way he leered at you.
他可没有
He did not.
至少他不像你家那位那么无趣
At least he's not boring.
既然我是那么喜欢和你呆在一起住
As much as I enjoy having you spend the night at my house,
咱们可不可以  就那么一次也好
could we please, for once,
谈论下除了你和Jonathan呆在一起
talk about something other than
多么无聊以外的事？
how tedious you find Jonathan?
再说一句  他并不无聊
And besides, he's not boring.
我想说的是
What I'm saying is that
她能找到一个更好的人选
she could do better.
你看到什么了吗？
Do you see anything?
没有啊。
No.
你说那是什么？
What do you suppose it is?
-晚安 Clive先生 -晚安
- Good night, Mr. Clive. - Good night.
马车 开走吧
Horse, move on.
啊！
Aah!
此人就是一猪猡
The man was a pig.
他在我的地界撒野
He insulted me under my own roof.
所以你就把他撕成碎片了？
So you tear the man to pieces?
也许我们要贴个警告牌
Perhaps we should mount a warning sign
在前门上
over the front door.
我早就告诉你
I told you,
他们的贪污腐败骄纵自大
their corruption
已经到了无法无天的地步
and their hubris is unbridled.
恶龙会一贯如此
That's always been the way with the Order of the Dragon.
但我们仍能觉察它的痕迹
Still, it's one thing to hear it,
用我们的眼睛就能察觉到
quite another to see it with one's own eyes.
从那对头衔
Readily identified by
急切到荒谬的执念
their overtly grotesque
就能清楚的发现是恶龙会的人
sense of entitlement.
就像这个家伙 Laurent大人
Like this one, Lord Laurent.
洋洋得意的孔雀男
Preening little peacock.
还有这个  大人  他叫什么名字？
And the other one, Lord what's-his-name?
- Davenport. - Davenport.
上院里的两个渣滓
These two stink of high council.
把他们的名字写在名单上
Put them on the short list.
您认为谁是他们的头子？
Who do you suppose is the leader?
可能是这名单里的任何一个
Could be any one of these.
也可能哪个都不是
Or none.
多么的乏味啊
How very innocuous.
可您已点燃他们的怒火 Renfiled
But you cross them, Renfield,
他们对您将如同
and they will strike you down
困在井中的蝮蛇一般凶残
like vipers in a pit.
谋杀 拷打 奸淫 灭门
Murder, torture, rape, wholesale slaughter.
这可都是恶龙会的惯用手法
That is the stock-in-trade of the Order of the Dragon,
说实在的用了五百年了
and has been for over 500 years.
在我年轻之时
In my past,
他们更加露骨的达成目的
they asserted their will more directly
用那弓与剑
via the cross and the sword,
整村一个不留
slaughtering entire villages,
给男男女女贴上异教徒的标签
branding men and women heretics.
啊！
Aah!
活活把他们烧死
Burning them alive,
眼睁睁的看着他们尖叫着被火焰吞噬
and watching them burn, screaming...
只是为了无人见过的主神
For a God who never came.
现在他们在私人俱乐部和会议室的掩护下
Now they do their dirty work
继续做着肮脏的勾当
via private clubs and boardrooms.
他们控制商业 贿赂政客 控制石油
They employ business, politics, and oil.
而最后的那个 Renfield
And that last thing, Renfield,
将会是他们的命门
will be their undoing.
他们相信
They believe
下个世纪将会在石油的滋养下蔓生
it will fuel the next century.
只要他们可以控制石油
And if they control it,
未来就是他们的
they control the future.
但从我们证实了
But from the moment we demonstrate
生物能源的可行性的那一刻起
the viability of geomagnetic technology...
呼！
Poof!
金钱就不会流进腰包
No more money.
权力也会离他们而去
No more power.
而恶龙会也将土崩瓦解
No more Order of the Dragon.
他已经充分检查过了？
He performed a full examination?
流程一点不差
As instructed.
从何看出是吸血鬼掠食的结果？
Any signs of vampiric feeding?
颈部损伤太大
Too much damage to the neck
无法判断
to make a positive determination.
所以他砍下了这个人的脑袋
So he severs the man's head
把他装扮成法国烤母鸡
and dresses him up like a roasted French hen.
不得不这么做
Well, it had to be done.
你知道的
You know why.
从何时起吸血鬼开始
How long has it been since a vampire stalked
在街头横行？ 七年前？
the streets of this city? Seven years?
八年了
Eight years.
噢  对  白教堂血案
Yes, the Whitechapel killings.
天啊  看看我们惹上的麻烦事
God, when I think of the trouble we went to,
毁尸灭迹
mutilating the victims to hide the signs,
还有那些我们写给报社的荒谬信件
those absurd letters we wrote to the press.
嗯  开膛手杰克
Huh. Jack the Ripper, indeed.
你想说什么?
What do you suggest?
除非有其他的证明
Well, unless proven otherwise,
不然我们必须假定Clive
I think we must assume that Clive
被我们的敌人袭击了
was targeted by our enemies,
不论看上去是否自然
whether natural or not.
我会安排Kruger巡逻
I will put Kruger on patrol.
让他盯紧理事
Have him keep an eye on the high council members' houses.
- 一直?  - 不是
- Indefinitely? - No.
直到时间与事实可以证明
Just until time or events
我们不过是孤独谨慎
proves us overcautious.
他在这儿你都不一定知道呢
You won't even know he's there.
记住别走漏风声
See to it that we don't.
这是我们两个人的秘密
This is strictly between you and me for now.
大家已经够紧张兮兮的了
We don't want to make the others any more nervous
- 我们不能让他们徒增烦恼  - 嗯
- than they already are. - Hmm.
如果有人问起
And if anyone asks
就说他是被狗咬死的
He was killed by a dog.
你上道了
Good girl.
别忘了血淋淋的东西
And take that bloody thing with you.
神经元组织
The structure of the neuron is absolutely distinct
同身体其他部位的细胞不一样
from all other cells in the human body.
Campbell先生?
Mister Campbell?
不好意思  我们…
Sorry, sir. We weren't, um...
Van Helsing教授?
Professor Van Helsing?
是的  Murray女士?
Yes, Miss Murray?
Campbell先生只是在向他的同事指出
Mister Campbell was only pointing out to his colleagues
新闻头版提到的电脉冲是如何产生的
how analogous certain aspects of the front-page article regarding
与您今天的讲课主题
the generation of electrical impulses
是如何相似
are to the subject of your lecture today.
Campbell先生?
Mister Campbell?
Campbell先生  相当正确
Quite right, Mister Campbell.
Grayson先生的新技术
Mister Grayson's new
和我今天要讲的主题有密切关系
technology is germane to the subject at hand.
但是  我建议你
However, I would suggest
在课外讨论这一观察成果
that you discuss such observations outside of class.
Grayson先生呆会儿会来
Mister Grayson will be right with you.
Harker先生
Mister Harker.
您能来真是太好了
How good of you to come.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
来点酒吗?
Would you like some wine?
好像早了点  谢谢
It's a, um, bit early for me, thank you.
我喜欢威士忌
I prefer whiskey.
您应该知道我的编辑
You should know my editor
认为您多少有吹牛的成分
believes you're after some sort of puffery.
- 吹牛?  - 是的
- Puffery? - Yes.
他怎么会这么想呢?
And why would he think that?
我没有采访过几次
I don't field many interview
像您这样有地位的人
requests from those in your position.
你是说富豪?
You mean the wealthy?
不  我是说权贵
No, I mean the privileged.
通常他们都会回避
Usually, they run the other way.
那是因为
That's because
你一旦和我有一样的既得利益
you stand against the same
就会希望我回美国
vested interests that would prefer I return to America.
我想没人注意到
I didn't think anyone had noticed.
我注意到了
I did.
这也是我请你来采访的原因
That's precisely why I invited you for this interview.
可以开始了吗?
Shall we begin?
好
Very well.
为什么是英国?
Why England?
这是我曾祖父母的家乡
This is the country of my great-grandparents' birth.
也就是归国
In that regard, it's a homecoming.
和Edison将你赶出美国
And it has nothing to do
没有一点关系?
with Edison running you out of the States?
欧洲人的说话方式别具一格
Europe speaks to me in a way no other place does.
这也是我们称之为"旧世界"的原因
You know, we call it "The Old World" For a reason.
但他们无论在哪都追求新事物
And yet, her people seek the new wherever they can.
我明白这种挣扎
I understand this struggle.
我是古老家族的后代
I, myself, am descended from a very old family.
但我的心里永远向往未来
But my mind, always fixed on the future.
我会用两种思维方式来思考
I surround myself with things that speak to both.
你很矛盾  对吧?
You're full of contradictions, aren't you?
世界原本就是矛盾的
So is the world.
这也是我想和你交流的原因
That is precisely why I wanted to talk to you.
我们在大变革的关口上
You see, we're on the precipice of a great change.
我们开始重新定义
We have it within ourselves
我们的物种
to redefine our species.
等等…  你说“物种”
Wait, you...You say "Species"
好像人是动物似的
As though people are animals.
这是什么意思?
What do you mean by that?
不是达尔文先生教我们的吗?
Is that not what Mister Darwin taught us?
进化论?
That man evolves?
这一理论就是我努力的原因
That is what I've come here to accomplish.
促进人类的演变
To facilitate in that evolution.
也就是说  帮助自然进化
Give nature a helping hand, so to speak.
- Murray女士  - 教授
- Miss Murray. - Professor.
进来吧  请坐
Come in. Have a seat.
有什么事?
What is it?
额  恩  我们
Well, um, we will soon be
就快期末考了
undergoing our final examination.
- 是的  - 你也知道
- Yes. - And as you know,
得分最高的学生
the student who scores the highest will be given
有机会成为你的研究助理
the opportunity to serve as your research assistant.
我明白了
I see.
你的分数一直是班上最高的
You have consistently scored the highest marks in class
不论是笔试还是口试
for every written and oral exam.
- 可是…  我的外科技术…
- However... My surgical technique...
仍然有待提高  没错
...leaves much to be desired, yes.
教授  您简直无法想象我练习了多少次
Professor, I can't tell you how often I practice,
但是每当手术刀要割破皮肤表皮的那一刻
but the moment the scalpel pierces the epidermis,
我就…
well...
不论我怎么做
my hands begin to tremble
我的手都抖个不停  他们…
and no matter what I do, they...
Mina…
Mina...
我发现
I have always found that
保持手不抖的秘诀
the secret to a steady hand
就是保持一颗平静的心
is a steady heart.
- 我不明白  - 你必须相信自己
- I don't understand. - You must believe in yourself,
相信以你的能力能够治愈别人
in your abilities to heal others.
就是这么简单
It is that simple.
我信自己
But I do.
既然如此  你会成功的
If so, then you will succeed.
到那时  你会明白…
Until then, know this...
心是不会说谎的
The heart never lies.
谢谢你
Thank you.
对  好的  我同意
Yes, well, I agree.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Well, good night. - Good night.
晚安
Good night.
你好
Hello.
抱歉让你等了这么久
Sorry to have kept you waiting here.
Grayson先生真是慷慨
It was very generous of
让你用他的包厢
Mister Grayson to give you his box tonight.
他只是想让我写点
Well, he obviously wants me
夸赞他的东西  不是吗？
to write nice things about him, doesn't he?
是吗？
Really?
像Grayson先生这样的人
A man such as Grayson is so desperate
竟然迫不及待地巴结你
to court favor with you?
他肯定对他那金碧辉煌的房子
You'd think he'd be satisfied with his beautiful home
还有那些优美的画作
and all those brilliant paintings
和高科技非常满意
and the thrilling technology,
更不要提他那漂亮的脸蛋
not to mention his good looks
和非凡的魅力
and charisma.
没错
Hmm.
的确令人印象深刻
Yes, it's very impressive.
但是你有他永远也没有的东西
But then you have something that he will never have.
是什么
What's that?
我
Me.
从这后面看视角更好点
The view is much better from back here.
是吗?  我从来不知道
Is it? I can't imagine that's possible.
和我一起看怎么样？
Why don't you join me and see?
对 没错 的确是惊人
Why, yes, it is. It is astonishing.
我觉得你是被冷落了
I trust you were unobserved?
你也确实要求我“谨慎”的陪伴
Your invitation did request my "Discreet company".
没错  虽然我还担心
Yes, it did. Though I was concerned,
你作为一个美国人可能会
as an American, that you might not understand
不理解“谨慎”的意思
the meaning of the word "Discreet."
我的确需要查字典看看
I had to look it up.
告诉我  还有什么词语
Tell me, what other words
是你需要查询的
did you have to look up?
贪婪无比
Insatiable.
无可救药
Incorrigible.
难以抑制
Unquenchable.
Clive先生下葬不到一天
Sir Clive not a day in the ground,
Grayson就像禽兽一样
and Grayson descends on his widow
打劫了他的妻子
like a bird of prey.
带走了Clive的整箱冷却剂
Locked up Clive's entire block of imperial coolant.
她为什么要卖给他？
Why on earth would she sell out to him?
他为Clive还清了赌债
He purchased the paper on Clive's gambling debts,
并要挟要起诉他的房产权
and threatened to sue his estate.
- 天啊!  - 所以她没有选择
- Good God! - So you see, she had no choice
只有接受交易以防丑闻外传
but to trade the stock in order to avert a scandal.
这整档子事真恶心
Absolutely loathsome, the whole damned business.
但你必须承认  很精彩
But you must admit, well played.
你说得轻松
That's easy for you to say.
他又不是你的商业伙伴
He's not your business partner.
那可不一定
Oh, he's hardly that, old man.
只是董事会的一个席位而已
It's just a seat on the board.
又不是控有股权
Not as if he has a controlling interest.
Kruger
Kruger.
地狱之火!
Burn in hell!
“死去的猎人兄弟
"Thou died fair and well,
安息吧”
brother huntsman killed."
“在你静寂前
"Impaled the hearts of many beasts,
已刺穿无数野兽的胸膛”
before thine own was stilled."
死之前
Before you die,
鼓起勇气
take heart.
很快就到地狱了…
You will soon be joined in hell...
同你的兄弟们一样
by scores of your brethren.
我会摧毁你们的秩序…
I will destroy your Order...
以及一切秩序代表
and everything it stands for.
你是…
You are...
Dracula
Dracula.
尽管练吧  但无法挽救你
Practice all you want. It won't save you.
说话了
It speaks.
挽救我什么？
Save me from what?
把你带到伦敦的人？
The one that drew you to London?
没人带我来
No one drew me.
你一无是处
You're nothing.
不过是被腐烂的臭味吸引的苍蝇
An errant fly attracted by the stench of rot.
告诉我你主人的名字！
Tell me your sire's name!
你知道你的物种是有宿命的
You know, there's fates for your kind
比死更糟  我清楚得很
a lot worse than death, and I know them all.
你以为在湖底腐蚀要话
How long do you think
需要多久的时间
it's going to take for this to rust
几年？  几十年？
at the bottom of a lake? Years? Decades?
随便你怎么样
Do what you will to me.
会有人紧跟其后
There will be another who follows,
不久之后  一个又一个 很快的
and another, and another, and soon...
不久之后？
Soon?
我们会成为一个军团
We will be legion.
我刚才在想你会什么时候进来
I was wondering when you'd make your entrance.
计划本来是让Clive大人的债务
The plan was to leverage
杠杆扩大
Sir Clive's gambling debts
违背他的利益
against his interests,
不是他的遗孀的利益
not his widow's.
我看到了一个机会
I saw an opportunity...
并抓住了这个机会
and I seized it.
你的行为冲动又鲁莽
It was impetuous and careless.
但任务完成了
It got the job done.
需要我解释多少次
How many times must I explain the difference
家族世仇和报复的不同？
between a vendetta and vengeance?
这不能演变为一场消耗战
This cannot become a war of attrition.
就像一条九头蛇
The Order Draco is like the Hydra.
切下一个蛇头  它会长出两个取而代之
Cut off a head, they grow two to replace it.
有趣
Funny.
发生在Clive大人身上的不是这样的
That's not what happened to Sir Clive's head.
别傻了
Don't be a fool.
你知道摧毁他们惟一的方法
You know the only way to crush them
就是消灭他们
is to wipe out
他们力量的特有来源
the very source of their power,
他们巨大的财富
their vast wealth.
十多年了
For over a decade
我们设计并建造了这座谎言帝国
we've schemed and built this empire of lies.
我不会允许因为你的缺乏纪律
I will not have our work undone
让我们的事业无法完成
by your lack of discipline!
啊！
Ah!
给我一个不把你的皮
Give me one good reason
像葡萄一样剥掉的好理由
I should not peel you like a grape.
要是没有我
Because without me,
你还在那个铁盒子里烂着呢
you'd still be rotting in that iron box.
你认为我会被激怒吗？
Do you think I am not immune to rage?
恶龙会屠杀了全部家人！
The Order of the Dragon slaughtered my entire family!
我们不能放弃自己的本能
We must not give in to our base instincts.
我们必须练习控制力
We must practice control.
- 我们必须按照计划行事  - 确实
- We must follow the plan! - True.
我们的憎恨
Our hatred
始于同一个严酷的考验
was born in the same crucible.
你赋予了它行事
You give it form.
但我赋予了它力量！
But I give it strength!
我们不是因为所失去的
We are not bound by
而结合在一起
what we have lost,
而是因为夺走的人
but by who took it!
不！
No!
他们杀死了我的妻子！
They killed my wife!
我的爱
My love.
因为这些罪行
For these crimes,
我一定会复仇
I will have my vengeance.